<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="notif0000">
            <item name="title">
                Luca Guadagnino and Daniel Craig Are in Talks to Make Superhero Debut with DC Studios’ ‘Sgt. Rock’
            </item>
            <item name="msg">
                Luca Guadagnino and Daniel Craig might have another novel adaptation in the works after collaborating together on “Queer.” But this rumored adaptation isn’t Burroughs; it’s actually a comic book.
                According to a Deadline report, auteur Guadagnino and lead star Craig are in talks to bring DC Studios‘ “Sgt. Rock” to the screen. Deadline noted that no deals have been confirmed between DC Studios, Craig, or Guadagnino. DC Studios did not respond to a request for comment.
                The character of Sgt. Franklin John Rock, assumed to be played by Craig given the report, was created by Robert Kanigher and Joe Kubert for the 1959 DC issue, “Our Army at War.” Like Craig’s “Queer” character, Rock is a WWII veteran. Rock landed his own comic book series, which ran from 1977 to 1988.
                Craig will be starring in the third “Knives Out” film, “Wake Up Dead Man: A Knives Out Mystery.” He reprises his role as detective Benoit Blanc in the Rian Johnson franchise.
                “Challengers” filmmaker Guadagnino, meanwhile, is in post-production on Amazon MGM Studios’ “After the Hunt, which stars Julia Roberts and Andrew Garfield. Guadagnino will next remake “American Psycho,” which is rumored to star Jacob Elordi. Scott Z. Burns (“Extrapolations,” “The Bourne Ultimatum”)
                will adapt Bret Easton Ellis’ novel for the screen. Christian Bale led the original 2000 film alongside Guadagnino’s frequent collaborator Chloë Sevigny; Mary Harron co-wrote and directed the classic film.
                Additionally, Guadagnino will work with his “Challengers” actor Josh O’Connor (who also stars alongside Craig in “Wake Up Dead Man”) for the “Separate Rooms” adaptation. Léa Seydoux is set to also lead the feature which is a queer drama based on the novel of the same name by late author Pier Vittorio Tondelli.
                O’Connor will play the lead role Leo, an Italian writer who is mourning the death of his musician boyfriend Thomas. Seydoux is the woman with whom Leo embarks on a relationship. Guadagnino’s “We
                Are Who We Are” collaborator Francesca Manieri is writing the script. “Separate Rooms” will be produced by Lorenzo Mieli under his deal with Fremantle, which was also behind Guadagnino’s “Bones and All” and “Queer.”
            </item>
            <item name="image">
                notif_image_0000
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="notif0001">
        <item name="title">
                ‘The Pope’s Exorcist’ Director Julius Avery to Helm Alien Abduction Thriller ‘They Found Us’ From AGC and ‘Smile’ Producers Temple Hill
        </item>
        <item name="msg">
                Julius Avery, the director of “Samaritan,” “Overlord” and “The Pope’s Exorcist,” has come on board to direct the new alien abduction thriller “They Found Us.” The film hails from “Smile” producers Temple Hill Entertainment and Stuart Ford’s AGC Studios, which is financing the project.
                AGC Intl. will handle international sales and co-rep U.S. rights with UTA Independent Film Group. Casting is underway on the movie, which will shoot in Australia in the first half of 2025.
                “They Found Us” follows a father and daughter who undertake a camping trip in the Utah wilderness to heal their broken relationship. Attacked by a hostile extraterrestrial life form, their lives, not just their relationship, are at stake as they fight with a humanoid beast to stop their abduction to an unknown and terrifying alien world.
                The film is based on an original screenplay by Jeremy Slater (“Moon Knight,” “Fantastic Four”), and will be produced by Godfrey and Marty Bowen for Temple Hill. Ford is on board as an executive producer along with Temple Hill’s John Fischer.
                Avery is an Australian filmmaker known for genre-bending action and horror films. His debut feature, “Son of a Gun,” starred Ewan McGregor and Brenton Thwaites. He gained early recognition with his short film “Jerrycan,” which won awards at Cannes, Sundance and Berlin. Avery’s second film, “Overlord” (2018), a WWII horror film produced by J.J. Abrams, starred Jovan Adepo and Wyatt Russell. It was followed by the Sylvester Stallone feature “Samaritan” and horror movie “The Pope’s Exorcist” starring Russell Crowe.
                Avery is repped by CAA and Brillstein Entertainment. Slater is represented by UTA, Kaplan/Perrone Entertainment and McKuin Frankel Whitehead. AGC’s exec VP of legal and business affairs Anant Tamirisa negotiated the deal on behalf of AGC and Hansen, Jacobson, Teller, Hoberman, Newman, Warren, Richman, Rush, Kaller, Gellman, Meigs and Fox negotiated on behalf of Temple Hill.
        </item>
        <item name="image">
            notif_image_0001
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="notif0002">
        <item name="title">
            ‘The Batman 2’ Delayed to 2027, Alejandro G. Iñarritu’s Tom Cruise Movie Gets 2026 Date
        </item>
        <item name="msg">
            Moviegoers will have to wait a little longer to return to Gotham City, as Matt Reeves’ follow-up to “The Batman” has been pushed back until 2027. The superhero sequel was originally supposed to open on October 2, 2026, but will now shift a year and open on October 1, 2027, in Imax, Warner Bros. announced on Friday.
            That left an opening for Alejandro G. Iñárritu and Tom Cruise‘s upcoming film to hit theaters in 2026, just as the awards season race kicks off. The film, which still lacks a title, will open in Imax on Oct. 2 in the date “The Batman 2” vacated.
            Warner Bros. made some additional tweaks to its upcoming release slate, swapping the openings of Bong Joon Ho’s “Mickey 17” and Ryan Coogler’s “Sinners.” Now, “Mickey 17,” which stars Robert Pattinson (who plays the Dark Knight in Reeves’ comic book series), will open on March 7, 2025, while “Sinners,” which re-teams
            Coogler with his “Black Panther” and “Fruitvale Station” star Michael B. Jordan, will shift back to April 18, 2025. That’s the date that “Mickey 17” was originally supposed to debut on, but the new release will allow Bong’s film to play longer in Imax, according to studio sources.
            The Cruise and Iñárritu film is shrouded in secrecy, but according to the official logline that Warner Bros. released it follows “the most powerful man in the world” as he “embarks on a frantic mission to prove he is humanity’s savior before the disaster he’s unleashed destroys everything.” The all-star cast includes
            Sandra Hüller, John Goodman, Michael Stuhlbarg, Jesse Plemons, Sophie Wilde and Riz Ahmed. Legendary Entertainment, the studio behind “Dune,” is producing the movie. It’s a change of pace for Cruise who has been busy saving the world in more conventional action films like “Mission: Impossible” and “Top Gun: Maverick.” Iñárritu
            is a two-time Oscar winner whose credits include “Birdman” and “The Revenant.” The pairing seems like a throwback to Cruise’s earlier career when he teamed up with A-list auteurs like Martin Scorsese, Steven Spielberg, Oliver Stone and Paul Thomas Anderson.
            “Mickey 17” follows a man (Pattinson), whose job is to die for a living. The cast includes Mark Ruffalo,  Naomi Ackie, Steven Yeun and Toni Collette. The film has had several release date shifts, and was originally intended to hit theaters in spring of 2024.
            “Sinners” is a horror film that features Jordan as twin brothers who return home to find “an even greater evil.” The ensemble also includes Hailee Steinfeld, Jack O’Connell, Wunmi Mosaku, Jayme Lawson, Omar Miller and Delroy Lindo. Shifting the date of “Sinners” was partly due to a shortage of post-production facilities to help put the
            finishing touches on the movie. “Sinners” was shot on film which exacerbated those issues.
            “The Batman” debuted in 2022 just as the movie business was shaking off the impact of COVID closures. It earned more than $770 million globally and was praised for its moody, atmospheric take on its title character. The film also inspired the HBO spinoff series “The Penguin.” In a recent sit-down with Zoë Kravitz, who appeared as Catwoman, Reeves
            said he was finishing the script for the sequel and planned “to be shooting next year.”
        </item>
        <item name="image">
            notif_image_0002
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="notifications">
        <item>@array/notif0000</item>
        <item>@array/notif0001</item>
        <item>@array/notif0002</item>
    </array>

</resources>